

Tomasz Mazurek

Address:
Żeromskiego 30a, Jastrzębie Zdrój
Phone:
+48 604 067 953
Email:
tomasz.a.mazurek@gmail.com

Summary

Programmer currently specializing in 3D graphics programming. Experienced with development of web and standalone applications. Well-versed in numerous programming languages, both in scripting and compiled, including JavaScript/Typescript, C/C++, Python, C#. Technology-agnostic, ready to jump in any project. Trying to use Design Patterns and S.O.L.I.D principles everywhere. Always ready for new problems to solve. Believes that no matter how hard it is, there is always solution. After hours experimenting with code, working on (beloved) games and his own game engine. Strong background in 3D graphics, networking, automotive area, management and customer relations.

Skills Highlight

Self-organized Complex problem solver Quick-learner

Self-starter Technology-agnostic Responsible

Competencies

Programming languages & methods	Experience	SkII-level (1-5)	Last used
Javascript (up to ES7)	3 years	4.5	3 months ago
Typescript	3 months	2.5	In current projects
GLSL	3 years	3.5	In current projects
C/C++	4 years	4	3 years ago
Python	2 years	3.5	2 years ago
C#	6 months	2.5	1 year ago
OOP	5 years	3.5	In current projects
Design patterns	3 years	2.5	In current projects

Tools & Frameworks & Libraries	Experience	Skll-level (1-5)	Last used
Three.js	3 years	4.5	In current projects
React	3 months	2.5	In current projects
WebGL/OpenGL	3 years	3	In current projects
Qt	1 year	2.5	2 years ago
Django	3 years	2.5	In current projects
Unreal Engine 4	1 year	3.5	In current projects
Unity	1 year	3.5	1 year ago

Experience

Professional:

Programmer (Javascript, remote job) - 03/2018 to 04/2020 **SelfCad**, New York

- Extending capabilities of CAD software by creating and implementing new tools.
- Developing new rendering methods using GLSL shading language.
- Desing and implementation of material and multimaterial system.
- Desing and implementation of light and shadow systems in scene.
- Desing and implementation of custom binary file format and serialization methods.
- Design and implementation of UI for tools and systems used in CAD application.
- Design and implementation of external material editor app using React and Typescript.
- Maintenance of existing code

Software Developer (C#) - 01/2018 to 03/2018

Advicom, Jastrzębie Zdrój

- Extending capabilities of MS Dynamics AX software with new tools and modules.
- Updating existing modules with new functionality
- Maintenance of existing code

IT support - 12/2016 to 12/2018

Advicom, Jastrzębie Zdrój

- Supporting end users of provided software
- Supporting end users of provided IT infrastructure

Bussines owner - 10/2007 to 11/2017

Euro Car, Jastrzębie Zdrój

- Managing automobile repair workshop
- Managing automotive parts shop
- Managing customer relations

Non-Professional:

Experiments and Side-projects - 2000 ->

- Material editor three.js/WebGL and Typescript/React
- Porfolio Website Python/Django and React

- Browser-based Video Chat app Javascript/WebRTC
- Multi-platform Game Engine C++/OpenGL
- Pirate Ship Simulation C++/Qt
- Train O Matic. Ticket Reservation System C++/Qt
- Tic Tac Toe game using recursive min/max algorithms C
- Space Shoter VR game C#/Unity
- Virtual DJ interactive music app in 3D C#/Unity
- RC Car controlled with Mobile Android App via bluetooth ATmega328p/C/Arduino library
- Restaurant Management Application C++/WPF
- Web BookStore Python/Django

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science - specialization: Internet and Computer Networks - 2020 Silesian University of Technology, Gliwice

Journalism/Economy – 1998 - 2000 Polonia University, Częstochowa

Automotive Technician: Automotive Technology – 1996 Vocational Automotive High School, Jastrzębie Zdrój

Languages

English - C1

Certifications

IT Support (certificate): CompTIA A+.

Resources

Google drive: https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ThzW03983Xft1KLwtpr4OhOVQI9pZt5o

Github: https://github.com/TomaszMazurek?tab=repositories **Linkedin**: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomasz-mazurek-b5248011

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych zawartych w mojej ofercie pracy dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997 r. o Ochronie Danych Osobowych; tekst jednolity z dnia 16.12.2015 r., Dz. U. z 2015 r., poz. 2135 z późn. zm.). Jednocześnie oświadczam, że zostałem/am poinformowany/a o dobrowolności podania danych osobowych, prawie dostępu do treści moich danych i ich poprawiania oraz prawie do odwołania zgody na przetwarzanie danych